你忘了还有我
Well, you're forgetting about me.
我也是你的竞争对手
I'm also your competition.
对 但是你平时都不在乎这些比赛
Yes,but you don't normally care about games like these.
但 我确实在乎这个比赛
Well, I do care about this game.
而且你输定了 因为我不是榆木脑袋
And you're gonna lose because my brains aren't made of hay.
我是脑袋脑袋
My brains are made of brains.
哦吼
Oh, ho.
完美的反驳
The perfect retort.
都过来 夹弟大赛要开始了
Gather up, it's Jimmy Jam time!
喔 你们要做开幕仪式吗
Ooh, are you doing opening ceremonies?
对 你可能得在状况激烈之前离开
Yeah, and you might wanna leave before things get too crazy.
一点点合理的推诿
A little plausible deniability.
实际上 我想录下来
Actually, I wanna record 'em.
也许你们能教教其他分局
Maybe you can teach other precincts
让他们举办各自的版本来鼓舞士气
how to throw their own versions to boost morale.
不 我才不是老师
No, I'm not a teacher.